Guide to the Amsterdam News photograph archive, Series B-MT, 1920-2012.
Amsterdam News photograph archive
- Series G. Contemporary File, 1988-2000
  - O'Connor, John (Box G-5, Folder 133)
    Photographer if identified: Joe Vericker/Photobureau Inc.
  - Octogenarian (Box G-5, Folder 134)
    With single-leaf ms. caption (separate from image). Print is a Polaroid.
    Photographer if identified: Mr. Laconia
  - O'Donnell, Rosie (Box G-5, Folder 135)
  - O'Leary, Hazel (Box G-5, Folder 136)
  - Olympic players (Box G-5, Folder 137)
  - O'Neal, Shaquille (Box G-5, Folder 138)
  - Ortiz, Felix W. (Box G-5, Folder 139)
  - "Out in New York" (Talk show) (Box G-5, Folder 140)
    Photographer if identified: Joe Sinnott
  - "Out of the South" (Box G-5, Folder 141)
    Photographer if identified: Jonathan Slaff
  - Owens, Jesse (Awards dinner) (Box G-5, Folder 142)
  - Owens, Major (Box G-5, Folder 143)
  - P (Box G-5, Folder 144)
    Also one image removed from an unidentified publication. 5 prints have staples through the border; 3 prints have staples through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Curt Clemons, Peterkin Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Leslie Barron, Joe Pineiro/Columbia University, Leon Salas, Chris Griffith
  - P (Box G-5, Folder 145)
    6 prints have staples through border; one print has staple through corner of image.
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, Pictorial Enterprise, Paulette Harley, Harris Photo, Chris Griffith, Roland E. Thomas, Wendy Workman, Curt Clemons, Shahar Azran
  - P (Box G-5, Folder 146)
    Also portion of a campaign mailing from Judge Preminger. One print is attached with a staple through the corner of the image to a 5-leaf press release from Pepsi dated 8-14-1991. One print is attached with a staple through the border to a 2-leaf press release on Prince Wooten dated 3-12-1990. 2 prints are paperclipped to 2 separate ms. notes signed by James Gilchrist Jr. dated 11-25-1991 (2 notes, each 1 leaf).
    Photographer if identified: Bob Head, Curt Clemons, George DuBose, Holly Rubi[na?], Pictorial Enterprise, Allen Morgan Photos, James Gilchrist Jr., Peterkin Photo, Abyssinian Baptist Church, Don W. Briggs/Perfect Pictures Studio, Karl Crutchfield, Curt Clemons
  - Jackson, Susan (Rev.) (Box G-6, Folder 147)
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Anita & Steve Shevett, Karl Crutchfield
  - N (Box G-6, Folder 148)
    Photographer if identified: Helen M. McDowell, Peterkin Photo, Bill Moore, Joanne Savio
  - O (Box G-6, Folder 149)
  - P (Box G-6, Folder 150)
    2 prints have staples through the border, 3 prints have staples through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Jeff Katz, Pictorial Enterprise, Curt Clemons, Peterkin Photo, Howie Evans, Carol Friedman, James J. Kriegsmann
  - P (Box G-6, Folder 151)
    Also one computer-printed image. One print has a staple through the border.
    Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Bill Moore, Lysa Allman-Baldwin, Risasi-Zachariah Dais, Josette Nozine, Hakim [Mutlaq], Christian Lantry, Howard T. Cash, Karl Crutchfield, Curt Clemons, Damaso Reyes
  - Page, Lisa (Box G-6, Folder 152)
  - Page, Treuds (Box G-6, Folder 153)
  - Panamanian (Box G-6, Folder 154)
    Prints are paperclipped to a 2-leaf faxed press release.
  - Parade (Box G-6, Folder 155)
    Also one computer-printed caption for a photo by George West (not present).
    Photographer if identified: Dmitri Gubin
  - Parades (Box G-6, Folder 156)
  - Parade of Stars (Box G-6, Folder 157)
  - Parade of Stars (Box OS-1)
    Lou Rawals Parade of Stars to Benefit the United Negro College Fund, group photos.
    Photographer if identified: Allen Morgan Photo & Video.
  - Parks Dept. and Giuliani (Box G-6, Folder 158)
  - Parks, Gordon (Box G-6, Folder 159)
    Both prints are stapled together, with staples through the top of the images, to an ms. note over the recto of the first print.
  - Parks, Gordon (Box G-6, Folder 160)
  - Parks, Gordon (Box G-6, Folder 161)
  - Parks, Gordon (Box G-6, Folder 162)
  - Parks, Rosa (Box G-6, Folder 163)
  - Pataki, George (Box G-6, Folder 164)
  - Pataki, George (Box G-6, Folder 165)
  - Pataki, George (Budget cuts) (Box G-6, Folder 166)
    Photographer if identified: Diane Greene, Karl Crutchfield
  - Paterson, David & Basil (Box G-6, Folder 167)
  - Paterson, David (Paterson Gallant wedding) (Box G-6, Folder 168)
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Bruce Williams
  - Patterson, John, Jr. (Box G-6, Folder 169)
    Photographer if identified: Ann Meuer
  - Payne, David (Box G-6, Folder 170)
  - Payne, Earl (Box G-6, Folder 171)
  - Peeple, Charles, III (Box G-6, Folder 172)
  - Peer, Kymberly (Box G-6, Folder 173)
  - People's Hall of Fame (Box G-6, Folder 174)
    Prints are attached together with a staple through the edge of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Martha Cooper
  - Perkins, Bill (Box G-6, Folder 175)
  - Petioni, Muriel (Box G-6, Folder 176)
  - Pettitt, Peggy (Box G-6, Folder 177)
    Photographer if identified: Dona Ann McAdams
  - Phifer, Mekhi (Box G-6, Folder 178)
  - Photographic Center of Harlem (Box G-6, Folder 179)
  - Pink (Box G-6, Folder 180)
  - Pinkett, Mary (Box G-6, Folder 181)
  - Pinkins, Tonya ("Play On") (Box G-6, Folder 182)
    Photographer if identified: Martha Holmes, Carol Rosegg
  - Pippen, Scottie (Box G-6, Folder 183)
  - Pleneros de la 21, Los (Box G-6, Folder 184)
  - Plummer, Denise (Box G-6, Folder 185)
  - Pocahontas (Box G-6, Folder 186)
  - Poitier, Sydney (Box G-6, Folder 187)
    Photographer if identified: Hakim Mutlaq
  - Police Rally (Box G-6, Folder 188)
  - Politics (Box G-6, Folder 189)
    Also 2 halftone prints. 2 prints have staples through corner of image.
    Photographer if identified: Tonayi Seabrook, Allen Morgan, Frank Solomon, Peterkin Photo, Christopher Griffith, Robert L. Haggins, Herman Merritt, John Crow
  - Pollution protesters (Box G-6, Folder 190)
  - Pope, Eljah (Dr. Rev.) (Box G-6, Folder 191)
  - Potts, Sammy (Dr.) (Box G-6, Folder 192)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, Jr. (Box G-6, Folder 193)
    Photographer if identified: Bill Moore, George Ballis/Take Stock
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, IV (Box G-6, Folder 194)
  - Powell, Adam Clayton, IV (Box G-6, Folder 195)
  - Powell, Colin (Box G-6, Folder 196)
  - Powell, Colin (Box OF-1, Folder 29)
  - Powell, Colin (Box OF-1, Folder 30)
    Photographer if identified: James Gilbert, Gerald E. Hayes, Karl Crutchfield
  - Powell, Doc (Box OF-1, Folder 31)
    Photographer if identified: Charlie Pizzarello
  - Powell, Kevin (Box OF-1, Folder 32)
  - Power of Three (Box OF-1, Folder 33)
    Photographer if identified: Pauline St. Denis
  - Powers, Betty (Box OF-1, Folder 34)
  - Prescott, Pat (Box OF-1, Folder 35)
  - President's Summit for America's Future (Box OF-1, Folder 36)
  - Price, Hugh (Box OF-1, Folder 37)
  - Price, Hugh (Box OF-1, Folder 38)
    Print is paperclipped to a single-leaf press release.
  - Price, Hugh (Box OF-1, Folder 39)
    Note on folder: "Urban League CEO."
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Gerald E. Hayes, Roy Lewis Archives, James Gilbert
  - Prince (Box OF-1, Folder 40)
    Also 3-leaf computer-printed article text "'The Artist' Rocks the Garden" by George R. Addison III. Note on folder: "Artist."
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, George R. Addison III
  - Professional Women of Color Anniversary Gala (Box OF-1, Folder 41)
    Prints are paperclipped to a single-leaf press release, a single-leaf faxed press release, and a computer-printed memo from Kimberly Powell (1 leaf).
  - Project Harmony (Box OF-1, Folder 42)
  - Protest (Box OF-1, Folder 43)
    Photographer if identified: Josette Nozine, Workers Vanguard, Norman Frederick, Damaso Reyes, Karl Crutchfield, James Gilbert
  - Protesters (Box OF-1, Folder 44)
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Karl Crutchfield
  - Protesters (Box OF-1, Folder 45)
    Photographer if identified: Peterkin Photo, Dan Steiger, Bill Moore
  - Protests (World fairness) (Box OF-1, Folder 46)
    Also one machine-printed contact sheet (18 images).
    Photographer if identified: Kristiana Jo Thomas
  - Proud Parents (Box OF-1, Folder 47)
  - Proud scholarship Winners (Box OF-1, Folder 48)
  - Public Enemy (Box OF-1, Folder 49)
    One single-leaf press release
  - Puente, Tito (Box OF-1, Folder 50)
  - Puerto Rico Rights (Box OF-1, Folder 51)
  - Puppet Man (Box OF-1, Folder 52)
  - Q (Box OF-1, Folder 53)
    Photographer if identified: Kenn Duncan
  - Q (Box OF-1, Folder 54)
    Also one 2-leaf press release biography of Florence Quivar. One print has a staple through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Kenn Duncan
  - Queen Latifah (Box OF-1, Folder 55)
  - R (Box OF-1, Folder 56)
    Also one computer-printed image and one newspaper clipping.
    Photographer if identified: Damaso Reyes, Ali Rahman, Louis Boone, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Brian L. Velenchenko, Nelson Kwok, Duane Michaels, Gerry Goodstein, Amun, John Horne, Eric Johnson, Debra Boardley, James Gilbert, Donovan R. Gopie, Douglas Foulke, Allen Morgan Photo Service, Tony Noel/Fifth Avenue Phototek, Risasi-Zachariah Dais, Lani Russell Lewter, Kerika Fields, Harris Photo
  - R (Box OF-1, Folder 57)
    Also one computer-printed image and one photocopied photo caption (not attached to any print). 3 prints have staples through the border; 2 prints have staples through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Karl Crutchfield, Milo Bocchetti, Bill Moore, Beverly Parker, Pictorial Enterprise, James Gilbert, Edward Reed, Karl Crutchfield, Corporate Photographers Inc., C. Love, Ali Rahman, Sharon Farmer, Curt Clemons, Bert Andrews, Peterkin Photo, Lavalais, Harris Photo
  - Raines, Franklin (Box OF-1, Folder 58)
  - Randle, Ian (Box OF-1, Folder 59)
  - Rangel, Alma (Box OF-1, Folder 60)
  - Rashad, Phylicia (Box OF-1, Folder 61)
  - Ray, Goodman & Brown (Box OF-1, Folder 62)
  - Reaves, Sandra (Box OF-1, Folder 63)
  - Red Apple Supermarket (100th St. and Columbus Ave.) (Fire) (Box OF-1, Folder 64)
  - Robinson, Jackie (50th Anniversary) (Box OF-1, Folder 65)
  - Russon, Laureen (Box OF-1, Folder 66)
  - Schwartz, Charles (Officer) (Box OF-1, Folder 67)
  - Thomas, Peter (Box OF-1, Folder 68)
  - Tribe Called Quest, A (Box OF-1, Folder 69)
  - Vanilla Ice (Box OF-1, Folder 70)
    All prints are stapled together through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Greg Gorman, John Johnson
  - West, Cornell (Box OF-1, Folder 71)
    Note on folder: "Professor of African-American studies at Harvard."
  - Young, A.S. ("Doc") (Box OF-1, Folder 72)
    Print is mounted on paperboard.
  - Pictures (Misc.) (Box OF-1, Folder 73)
    Also one computer-printed image and one image removed from an unidentified publication. 2 prints have staples through the corner of the image. 2 prints are stapled together through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: George West, Pierre Noel Legagneur, Karl Crutchfield, Bill Moore, Kwame Brathwaite, L. Edwin Russell, Lani Russell Lewter, Hakim [Mutlaq], Allen Morgan, James Gilbert, David D. Roberts, Donovan R. Gopie
  - Pictures (Misc.) (Box OF-1, Folder 74)
    Also one contact sheet (12 images) and color slide.
    Photographer if identified: Damaso Reyes, Allen Morgan/Allen Morgan Photo Service, Bill Moore, Karl Crutchfield, Gerald Peart, George West, James Gilbert, David C. McNair, Lani Russell Lewter, Sarah Wells/Courtesy AFA, William Ramos/City of Newark, Peterkin Photo, Chris Rogers, Joseph Sinnott
- Series H. Transfer File, 1960s-1970s
  An alphabetic sequence of topical files with bulk material dates from the 1960s-1970s.
  - Amusement Parks (Box H-1, Folder 1)
  - Autos 1976 (Box H-1, Folder 2)
    Also one velox print. Two prints are attached to a single-leaf press release with a paperclip. One print has a staple through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Mazda Motors of America (East) Inc., Oldsmobile Public Relations
  - Autos 1977 (Box H-1, Folder 3)
    Also one press release (ca. Jan. 1982) (5 leaves). Two prints are stuck together with tape.
  - Autos 1978 (Box H-1, Folder 4)
    Three prints have staples through the border. Three prints have staples through the image.
    Photographer if identified: Dodge News Photo, Chevrolet Public Relations
  - Autos 1980 (Box H-1, Folder 5)
    Also one press release dated 1-27-1981 (3 leaves) and one color offset-printed promotional card.
    Photographer if identified: Pontiac Motor Public Relations, Oldsmobile Public Relations
  - Autos 1980 (Box H-1, Folder 6)
    Also one color offset-printed promotional card. One print has a staple through the border.
  - Buildings (Box H-1, Folder 7)
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, James Gilbert, Bert Andrews, Dave Greene, United Press International Inc., Bill Price, Lensman Photo
  - Children (Folder 1) (Box H-1, Folder 8)
    Two prints stuck together with paste. One print has staple through corner of image.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, L. St. Clair Dummett, Dave Greene Photo/Portfolio International Inc., A. Hansen, Taylor Oliver, George W. Martin, Chuck Lewis, Bill Price, Studio One
  - Children (Folder 1) (Box H-1, Folder 9)
    Also one halftone print. One print has staple through border.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Vince Antolini, King Photographers, Dalman James, That Magic Moment/Adeyemi Lythcott, Alan Perlman Photography, Peterkin Photo
  - Children (Folder 2) (Box H-1, Folder 10)
    Also 4 velox prints. Two sets of two prints are stuck together with paste. One print is a Polaroid.
    Photographer if identified: Wagner International Photo, Harris Photo, SEIMC-NYC-BOE, Dave Greene Photo, David Christopher McNair, A. Hansen, Newell Johnson, George W. Martin, United Press International Inc.
  - Children (Folder 2) (Box H-1, Folder 11)
    Also 13 velox prints.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Jarret Lee, Michael Grice Photography, Harris Photo, Greene Photo, Willard Smith, Bob Head, Dave Greene Photo
  - Children (Folder 2) (Box H-1, Folder 12)
    Also one printed image removed from an unidentified publication.
    Photographer if identified: Council on Adoptable Children, Harris Photo, Dave Greene Photo, CeeDee David, Clarence Davis, Wagner International Photos Inc., Miles Film Service, L. Robinson, Coreen Simpson, Tyrone Rasheed, Layton Ledgister, L. St. Clair Dummett, Bob Dawson, Pictorial Enterprise
  - Children (Folder 3) (Box H-1, Folder 13)
    5 prints are Polaroids. One print has staple through corner of image. Two prints are stuck together with paste. Also one halftone print.
    Photographer if identified: A. Hansen, A. Hinton, Wagner International Photo, Scott L. Henderson, Bill Price, Pictorial Enterprise, Lem Peterkin
  - Children (Folder 3) (Box H-1, Folder 14)
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Lem Peterkin, Bill Price, Dave Greene Photo, Harry Kalmus, Burgin, Studio One, Bob Head, Lesly Rock, Harris Photo
  - Children (Folder 3) (Box H-1, Folder 15)
    One print has staple through edge of image.
    Photographer if identified: Dunlap Turney, Greene, Peterkin Photo, Donald H. Mader, Pictorial Enterprise, Lensman Photo, Dave Greene Photo, Allen Morgan, Alex Summers, James C. Campbell
  - Church activities (Box H-1, Folder 16)
    Note on folder: "Awards, choirs, dedications, members, singing groups, services." Also 12 negatives (17 images) and one velox print. One print has staple through border.
    Photographer if identified: Dave Greene Photo, James Gilbert, King Photographers, Al Burley, Alex Hamilton, Bro David McAdams, Dept. of Foreign Missions/A.M.E. Zion Church, O.B. Willis, A. Hansen, James C. Campbell, DMNA Photo, Harris Photo, Herbert Hawkins, Dummett, Ernest Agnew, Bob Head
  - Church activities (Box H-1, Folder 17)
    Note on original folder: "Awards, choirs, dedications, members, singing groups, services." Also one velox print. One print has banquet invitation attached with staple through border. Two prints are mounted on paperboard.
    Photographer if identified: Bro. David McAdams, King Photographers, Hairston Photo, Al Burley, Harris Photo, A. Hansen, Gene Ward, Bill Carter, Bill Hayes Photography, Pope's Studio, Bill Foreman, L. St. Clair Dummett, Henry's Photo Studio,, Nichols/Rapid News Photo, Community Photo Studio
  - Church activites (II) (Box H-1, Folder 18)
    Note on folder: "Awards, choirs, dedications, members, singing groups, services." Two prints are attached with a paperclip to an autograph letter signed by Eve G. Morris dated 11-6-1976 (1 leaf). 2 prints have staples through the border, 3 through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Hayes Photography, Dave Greene Photography, Newell Johnson, Lensman, King Photographers, Pictorial Enterprise, Coreen Simpson, L. St. Clair Dummett, Baker Photo, Gene Ward, Harris Photo
  - Church activites (II) (Box H-1, Folder 19)
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Lem Peterkin, U.S. Army Photographer, King Photographers, A. Hansen Photography, Harris Photo, Dummett/Rapid News Photo, Norman Frederick, Dave Greene Photo, Al Galloway, Bill Hayes Photography, Bob Head, Bill Price, Collis Davis Photo, Studio One
  - Church activites (II) (Box H-1, Folder 20)
    One print has a staple through the border; three prints have staples through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Lensman Photo, King Photographers, Bryan D. Hall, Pictorial Enterprise, A. Hansen Photography, Paul Winik Photography, Bro. David McAdams, SUNY University Affairs, Bill Hayes Photography, BPI/Photo, Ernest C. Withers, Peterkin Photo, Gill Photographer
  - Church Ministers (Box H-1, Folder 21)
    Also one velox print and one halftone print. One print is attached with a paperclip to a typed letter signed by D.D. Garrett to the Amsterdam News dated 10-20-1972 (1 leaf) and a photocopied text titled "North Carolina Honors the Late James Walker Hood" (2 leaves). 3 prints are attached with a paperclip to the title page only of the pamphlet "Souvenir Journal in Tribute to Dr. Edward H. Boyce..." One print is a Polaroid.
    Photographer if identified: Bill Hayes Photography, King Photographers, United Church of Christ Office of Communication, Pope's Studio, James Gilbert, A. Hansen Studio, Arnold Katz Photography Inc., Vannucci Foto-Services, Norman, James C. Mooney, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Hayes Photography, David McAdams, BPI/Photo, L.O. Rogers Photo Studio, L. St. Clair Dummett, News Events Photo Service, City of Roanoke Office of the Mayor, Portfolio International Photographers/Dave Greene Photo, Alex Summers, Bill Berry
  - Church Ministers (Box H-1, Folder 22)
    Also two velox prints, five halftone prints, and one image removed from an unidentified publication. One print is mounted on paperboard. 2 prints are Polaroids. Two prints are stuck together with paste.
    Photographer if identified: Ernest C. Withers, Cameron, A. Hansen Studio, Bro. David McAdams, Studio Reneé, Pope Studio, Gill Photographers, Carl Purcell/Peace Corps, Hughes Studio, Bob Mobley, James Gilbert, The Photo Gallery, Harris Photo, Larry Karabaic, Wonder Photo, Levi B. Walters, Bill Mitchell Photography, Bill Hayes Photography
  - Church Ministers (Box H-1, Folder 23)
    Also one velox print and 2 halftone prints. One print has a staple through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Gill Photographers, SUNY University Affairs, Bryan D. Hall, Hill's Studio, Pictorial Enterprise, Peter G. Holden, Hayes Photo Service, Dummett, Harris Photo, Pope's Studio, Foto Caribe, Gene Ward, Hayes/L.I.P.P.A., F. Williams Photography, Hamilton Associates, A. Hansen Studio, L. St. Clair Dummett
  - Churches (Buildings) (Box H-1, Folder 24)
    Also three velox prints. One print is a Polaroid.
    Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Walter B. Baker, Dummett, Pictorial Enterprise, Bill Price, Dave Greene Photo, A. Hansen Photography
  - Clean-Up Campaign (Box H-1, Folder 25)
    Also two velox prints, one press release dated 6-29-1974 (1 leaf), and one "Litter Here" print. One print has photocopied press release (2 leaves) attached with a paperclip. 2 prints have staples through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Burley Photo Syndicate, Wagner International Photos Inc., King Photographers, Powell Photo, Bro. David McAdams, Reeves Studios
  - Clean-Up Campaign (Box H-1, Folder 26)
    Also 2 velox prints. 2 prints are stuck together with paste.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Harris Photo, Luigi, Dave Greene Photo, Layton Ledgister, Smooth Gary, King Photographers, James Gilbert, Bloomingdale House of Music, Bilal Farid/Priscila Taylor Ents., George W. Martin, Brad Hess Photography
  - Contest Winners (Box H-1, Folder 27)
    One print has a staple through the border; 2 prints have staples through the corner of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Bryan Hall, Bill Cancellare, Bro. David McAdams, Lensman, Cheryl Miller, A. Hansen, King Photographers
  - Corn Rows (Box H-1, Folder 28)
    Photographer if identified: A. Hansen Photography, Harris Photo, Ronnie Brathwaite
  - Crafts (Box H-1, Folder 29)
  - Farming (Box H-1, Folder 30)
    Photographer if identified: Ahmadu Wachuku
  - Fashion (Box H-1, Folder 31)
    Also one page showing clothing designs, removed from an unidentified publication.
  - Fashion (Box H-1, Folder 32)
    Also one photocopied image and one color slide (mounted on cardstock). Two prints are stapled together at the center of the image.
    Photographer if identified: Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Miami Beach Visitor and Convention Authority, Bob Head, Barry Rosenthal, Bob Brooks, Rich Rags
  - Fashion (Box H-1, Folder 33)
    Title on folder: "Fashions (Folder 1)." Also two velox prints. Two prints are stapled together.
    Photographer if identified: Coreen Simpson, Buddy Willis, Alan Perlman Photography, Dave Greene Photo, Kwame Brathwaite
    Number of Prints: 59
  - Fashion (Box H-2, Folder 1)
    Title on original folder: "Fashions (Folder 1)." Also one postcard. 2 prints are stuck together with tape. One print has a staple through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Norman Frederick, Lee Luckett, Coreen Simpson, Pictorial Enterprise
  - Fashion (Box H-2, Folder 2)
    Title on original folder: "Fashions (Folder 1)." Also one velox print. One print has a staple through the border.
    Photographer if identified: Pictorial Enterprise, Dave Greene Photo, Champaign Associates, Bill Price, Roland Harrison
  - Fashion (Box H-2, Folder 3)
    Title on original folder: "Fashion (Folder 2)." Note on original folder: "See also transfer file on left hand side of grey bookcase." Also one photocopied image and two images removed from an unidentified publication.
    Photographer if identified: Coreen Simpson, Harris Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Ira N. Golden, United Press International Inc., Mike M. Miyata/Long Island Jewish-Hillside Medical Center Community Relations Dept.
  - Fashion (Box H-2, Folder 4)
    Title on original folder: "Fashion (Folder 2)." Note on original folder: "See also transfer file on left hand side of grey bookcase." 3 prints are stuck together with paste. Also one velox print and one image removed from an unidentified publication.
    Photographer if identified: WDP Photo, Pictorial Enterprise, Barry Rosenthal, Coreen Simpson, Kwame Brathwaite, Clayton Hall, Bill Price, Dalman, Harris Photo
  - Fashion (Box H-2, Folder 5)